It's the last thing you'll see.
Smile 2 is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Parker Finn.
About to embark on a new world tour, global pop sensation Skye Riley begins
experiencing increasingly terrifying and inexplicable events.
Overwhelmed by the escalating horrors and the pressures of fame, Skye is forced to face her
dark past to regain control of her life before it spirals out of control.
Skye Riley, played by Naomi Scott.
Elizabeth Riley, played by Rosemarie DeWitt.
Lewis, played by Lukas Gage.
Joshua, played by Miles Gutierrez-Riley.
Morris, played by Peter Jacobson.
Paul Hudson, played by Ray Nicholson.
The film explores themes of drug dealer,
depression, new york city, dancing, suicide.
The tone is intense and mind_bending and dark.